[instrumental music]
Okay, everything is just
perfect. Oh, this is great.
They're coming, they're coming!
Come on, everybody, come on.
Okay, is everybody ready?
- Ready!
- Shh.
[whispering]
I'm sorry.
- Okay, let's go.
- Alright, get ready.
(all)
Surprise!
Thank you! Ha ha ha.
Why are they doing this?
- I don't know.
- Boys, come with me.
Today is the anniversary of
the day we all became a family.
As you know, you guys moved in
here a couple years ago
to help me out
for a couple months.
Now of course,
you can never leave.
Well, well,
let me tell you guys something.
We're happy to be here.
We love you very much.
- We can never leave?
- That's right.
And to celebrate, I have planned
seven days and seven nights
of non-stop family fun.
- Alright.
- Sounds good.
In Hawaii.
- Yay!
- Hawaii!
Hawaii? I love their punch.
I got the station to run reruns
of "Wake Up, San Francisco."
Well, Becky, you'll be able to
go with us. Come with us then.
Oh yeah, Becky, you and I
would have so much fun.
Oh, no, it sounds
like a family vacation.
- I got your ticket right here.
- Aah! Oh, Danny.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Oh, Jess,
you and me in Hawaii.
I know.
This is gonna be great.
We'll make a pilgrimage
to every single spot
where Elvis shot
"Blue Hawaii" in '61
and "Paradise, Hawaiian Style"
in '65.
Oh, Becky, what could be
more romantic?
[chuckles]
I'll start making a list.
Michelle, isn't this exciting?
We're going to Hawaii.
Good. Cut the cake.
[John Stamos singing
"Everywhere You Look"]
♪ Whatever happened
to predictability ♪
♪ The milkman
the paperboy evening TV ♪
♪ When did I get to living here
somebody tell me please ♪
♪ This whole world's
confusing me ♪
♪ Clouds as mean
as you've ever seen ♪
♪ And a bird
that knows your tune ♪
♪ And a little voice
inside you whispers ♪
♪ Kid don't sell
your dreams so soon ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Everywhere you go ♪
♪ There's a heart ♪
♪ A hand to hold on to ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Everywhere you go ♪
♪ There's a face
of somebody who needs you ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ When you're lost out there
and you're all alone ♪
♪ A light is waiting
to carry you home ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Dooby do ba ba dow ♪♪
[instrumental music]
- 'Yes, we're here.'
- Say aloha.
- Wooh!
- Come on, say cheese.
- Alright.
- Take a picture. Here we go.
- Hey, guys.
- Yes, yes, click, click, click.
Say cheese.
Let's go. Say cheese.
[indistinct chattering]
Aloha.
- Ah!
- Careful.
Uh, nice day.
Look, look,
Hawaii has a swimming pool
and an ocean,
and a soda machine.
No wonder they call it paradise.
Aloha, little girl.
Aloha, lady.
I see your belly button.
[instrumental music]
Joey. Joey.
Did you see that girl?
First she smiled at me.
And then she winked at me,
and then she..
...turned into someone else.
I hate when that happens.
Okay, I have plans for you guys.
- Catch you later.
- See you later.
Yo, calling all Tanners.
Where's everybody goin'?
- Surfing.
- Swimming.
I gotta find that hula girl.
We're gonna take the same drive
that Elvis took
in "Blue Hawaii."
We are?
Everybody, just calm down.
You are all gonna get to do
everything you want to.
But, and this is the beauty part
we are all gonna do
everything together.
(all)
Why?
That's a good start.
We came here to celebrate
our two-year anniversary
as one big, happy family,
so I have carefully scheduled
every minute of everyday
with everyone's activities.
It's all right here
on my clipboard of fun.
Ladies and gentlemen,
let the vacation begin.
Alright, we only have 15 minutes
to check in. Let's go.
You sure nobody else
wants to play golf?
(all)
No.
(Danny)
'Okay, Joey had his turn
for fun.'
'Now I've scheduled us
to study'
'the history
and culture of Hawaii.'
(Jesse)
'Where are you taking us?
The Don Ho Museum?'
Look, a little hula munchkin.
No, it's a Menehune.
According to the ancient legend,
they were the first people
to inhabit the Hawaiian islands.
The Menehunes
have magical powers
and they help people
when they're in trouble.
But only if you really
believe in them.
I do believe.
I wanna meet a Menehune.
Steph,
Menehunes are make-believe.
- Like Mickey Mouse.
- Oh yeah?
Then how come at Disneyland,
we shook hands with Mickey?
Did you shake hands
with a make-believe mouse?
No. Well, yeah. I don't know.
I think you do know.
Poor kid,
can't tell the difference
between real and make-believe.
Alright, everybody, we have
an hour and 20 minutes
to meet and greet over
57 varieties of marine life.
- Alright.
- Yeah!
[instrumental music]
Becky, get a picture!
Tell him to swim
more to his left.
It's a killer whale.
You tell him.
Nice fishie.
Big fishie.
Wait a minute!
Okay, yeah, hold on, honey.
'Hang on, girls, those things
don't come with seatbelts.'
[screaming]
[music continues]
(Danny)
'It's totally rad.'
'It's all on tape.'
[alarm beeping]
Okay, time's up.
Everybody, out of the pool.
[whistling]
Not you guys!
Right, this might be it.
Hang on a second.
This is it, folks.
This is the exact tree
Elvis floated by singing
"Drums Of The Island"
in his 1965 Technicolor classic
"Paradise, Hawaiian Style."
Please, just take a moment.
And let it all soak in.
Well, I'm soaked. Let's go.
Becky, please.
Show a little respect.
This is a historical
Elvis landmark.
Now, take some pictures.
'Thank you.
You're a beautiful family.'
Alright, get one with the real,
kinda whole lip thing.
Right here, baby.
He nuts.
(all)
Stroke! Stroke! Stroke! Stroke!
[instrumental music]
My girl!
[music continues]
She's gone!
And I'm alone.
And I'm wet.
(Danny)
'The clipboard of fun says
today, I get to be the skipper.'
(D.J.)
'Skipper, we've been out here
for hours.'
(Jesse)
'Danny, do you even
have a clue where we are?'
Ahoy, mateys.
Gather round ye skipper.
Aye aye, skipper.
According to my map,
we should be arriving any minute
at the beautiful island of Pua
for a picnic on the beach,
and a Polynesian show.
- Which island?
- This island.
- Hey, where did the island go?
- It's on your finger, dad.
Ahoy, mateys, your skipper's
been sailing all morning
to a potato chip crumb.
- Oh!
- Great.
- Dad, are we lost?
- Of course not.
[chuckles]
We're exactly, uh,
two hours and 46 minutes due..
...this way of our hotel.
Look, an island.
Alright, you see.
I told you.
Skipper, exactly
where is that island on the map?
Well, it's right..
Uh, it's, uh, one of those.
(Danny)
What a beautiful beach.
Anybody find anything?
(Rebecca)
Nothing up the beach.
There's nothing down the beach.
I haven't seen one sign
of intelligent life, skipper.
Whoa-ho! Island crankiness.
Look, nobody panic.
Let's just go back to where
your skipper tied up the boat.
I'll simply radio the coast
guard and tell him our location
and they'll guide us to Pua.
Okay? Now follow me.
- Aye aye, skipper.
- Michelle, don't encourage him.
(Danny)
Okay, guys, we're gonna
have our picnic on the boat.
Now, if the trade winds
are favorable
we can still make
the Polynesian show.
Of course, if we're late,
this could spell disaster
for the clipboard of fun.
- Bye-bye, boat.
- How cute.
Michelle's waving bye-bye to...
our boat!
Oh, D.J., don't be silly,
I tied up our boat right..
...there!
It is our boat.
- Come back!
- Hurry, dad.
Jesse, you'll never catch
that boat!
I don't wanna catch the boat.
I wanna catch Danny.
(Jesse)
Come back here.
(Danny)
'Jesse, leave me alone.'
Come over here, skipper.
- Not until you calm down.
- Fine. Alright. Fine.
I'm calm. I'm cool.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
- I just wanna talk to you.
- That's better.
First thing I'd like to say is
I hate this clipboard of fun.
How can a person lose a boat?
It's not my fault.
The rope must have slipped off
the rope thingy.
The rope thingy, skipper?
We're stuck.
What are we gonna do?
Well, if we were
on Gilligan's Island
the professor would make
a radio out of coconuts.
Joseph, it's no time for comedy.
It's time to blame Danny.
Relax, Jess, we have the rest
of our lives to blame Danny.
Right now, we need to keep
things light and easy
so the girls don't get scared.
So I don't get scared.
Are we in really big trouble?
(together)
No.
If we believe in the Menehunes,
they will come and help us.
And then, we'll live happily
ever after.
Seven year olds.
Aren't they adorable?
Don't ever pet me.
Oh, we better start looking
for food, shelter, water
and some Krazy Glue 'cause
I know I'm gonna break a nail.
- Alright.
- Hey, what the heck is this?
The clipboard comes back
but the boat keeps goin'.
Come on, let's go to work.
We got a lot to do, you guys.
- Come on, let's go.
- Okay.
Well, I hate to say it, Michelle
but the old skipper
really goofed up big time.
It's okay, skipper.
Oh, thanks, little buddy.
[Joey imitating Popeye]
Oh, a nice little coconut here,
a nice little one here..
Oh, boy, gosh..
Let's see here, huh?
Here goes..
Oh, gosh!
[instrumental music]
Oh, wow!
Joey.
Oh, yes!
Oh, gosh.
Seein' girls out in the water.
Gettin' conked on the noggin
with a coconut.
I'll bet you Bluto's got
somethin' to do with this, ooh.
Alright, fresh water.
A lot of fresh water.
It's beautiful.
Jesse, this is so romantic.
Kiss me.
That's "Paradise,
Hawaiian Style," little momma.
Jesse, we're finally alone
and you're still talking
about Elvis. Enough.
What's the matter?
You got a problem with the King?
The King made the exact
same movie 33 times.
The only thing that changed
were those stupid sideburns.
Hold it a second,
are you trying to tell me
that you have a problem
with Elvis' sideburns?
Yes, I believe
that's what I just said.
Well, well, well,
after all these months
the truth finally comes out.
You hate Elvis Presley.
Oh, no, not at first,
but you pushed me too far.
You know what your problem is?
You're jealous.
You're jealous 'cause Elvis
has better hair than you do.
- Better hair?
- Yeah, check a mirror.
- Oh, you know what?
- What?
I don't have to stand here
and listen to this.
Hey, I'm talkin' to you. Becky!
[shouting]
Becky!
[indistinct]
Look, Mr. Bear, orange things.
You taste them first.
[both screaming]
Menehune.
D.J.! D.J.!
Wait a minute.
I caught a..
...clipboard of fun.
(Stephanie)
'D.J., come here.'
I saw, we screamed..
I need...to catch...my breath.
Okay. I'm ready.
We're saved. I saw a Menehune.
I do believe. I do  believe.
I do believe you've been
in the sun way too long.
How rude.
It wasn't just me.
Mr. Bear saw him too.
Steph, your only witness
has buttons for eyeballs.
Trust me,
there are no Menehunes.
Well, if that's true,
then what's gonna happen to us?
We have no house,
or a bed, or a phone.
We can't even call out
for pizza.
We're doomed.
We're not doomed,
dad, Uncle Jesse and Uncle Joey
would never let
anything happen to us.
They have everything
under control.
- Are you sure?
- I'm sure.
There's nothing to worry about.
Thanks, Deej.
- Danny, what are you doing?
- This island is a pigsty.
Daddy, the plane, the plane.
[plane droning]
(both)
The plane! The plane!
(all)
Help! Help! Over here!
Help! Over here! Help!
(Jesse)
'They can't hear us.
They're gone.'
We're gonna be stranded
on this island forever.
Oh, and I suppose that's
my fault? Don't answer that.
I'll answer it.
Of course, it's your fault.
I'd say we leave you
and start our own tribe.
What's it gonna be? The tribe
of Elvis impersonators?
- Oh, that's really funny.
- All you talk about is Elvis.
- Enough with the Elvis stuff.
- Elvis this, Elvis this..
- It's not my fault, Joey.
- It is your fault.
D.J., I thought you said they
have everything under control.
Stop fighting.
We're all in this together.
The whole reason for this trip
was to celebrate being a family.
'We're lucky
to have each other.'
I bet if we start
working together as a team
we can make
Potato Chip Crumb Island
a totally rad place to hang.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I'm very proud of you, Deej.
Come on, let's do it, guys.
Alright, fellas, let's do it.
I say the heck with Elvis.
Let's build a hut, everybody,
alright?
And we can call it
the Grassland.
Thanks for saying that, D.J.
Michelle was looking
a little worried.
Not me.
- Come on.
- Let's go built a hut.
[instrumental music]
I'd like to make a toast.
Here's to dad,
Uncle Jesse and Joey, and Becky
for building
our beautiful new home.
- Thank you.
- Alright.
And for being the best big
sister on this whole island
here's to D.J.
(all)
Yay!
Here to Big Bird!
[drumbeats]
It's the Menehunes.
We're saved.
Come on, everybody.
Steph-Stephanie,
wait a minute, honey.
- Hold on, it's dark out there.
- Come..
Steph!
[drumbeats]
Don't worry. The Menehunes
are very cute and friendly.
[all screaming]
Or not.
[speaking in foreign language]
Alright. Leave the women
and children, just take the men.
Actually, just take the man
responsible.
Uh, excuse me, sir. I don't mean
to pry, but where are we?
- Pua.
- Pua? We're here.
See, the skipper got us
to the right island.
Just the wrong side of it.
You must be the owners
of the boat that washed ashore.
Sorry if we scared you but
we like to tease the tourists
before we put them onstage.
Pretty funny, aye?
[all laughing]
What is this?
(male announcer)
'This is Polynesia
invites our visitors'
'to join us onstage
for Tahitian dancing.'
[drumbeats]
Aloha.
Hey, it's you! I've been
lookin' all over for ya.
- Do you like to dance with me?
- Read my hips.
Read mine first.
[no audio]
[drumbeats]
[cheering and applauding]
Excuse me.
I talked to the band.
This one's for you,
and for Elvis.
"Rock-A-Hula" your heart out,
baby.
But the band knows the song?
[cheering and applauding]
[singing "Rock-A-Hula"]
♪ Rock-a-hula
rock rock-a-hula ♪
♪ Rock-a-hula rock ♪
♪ A hula rock a hula rock
a hula rock a hula rock ♪
♪ The way she moves her hips
to her fingertips ♪
♪ I feel I'm heaven bound ♪
♪ And when she starts to sway
I've gotta say ♪
♪ She really moves
the grass around ♪
♪ Rock ♪
♪ A hula baby ♪
♪ Got a hulu lulu
from Honolulu ♪
♪ Yeah that rock-a-hulu
baby of mine ♪
♪ Rock ♪
♪ A hula baby ♪
♪ Got a hulu lulu
from Honolulu ♪
♪ Yeah that rock-a-hulu
baby of mine ♪
♪ And I'm sayin' now rock ♪
♪ A-hulu baby ♪
♪ You're mine ♪♪
[cheering and applauding]
(male narrator)
Northwest Airlines with a proud
new look was pleased
to provide travel to Hawaii
for "Full House."
Northwest Airlines to more than
200 cities in 21 countries.
Accommodations
and locations provided
by Turtle Bay Hilton
and Country Club.
[theme music]